( Support Admin Watch on kissFlix.co )
[Genius Girlfriend]
[Episode 27]
Shen Fuxuan is
the only one absent today, right?
He has a shift at the hospital.
He told me about it.
Listen to this.
It's good to be busy. Let him be.
Listen.
Sorry, guys.
I'm on duty today
and really can't make it.
I'll treat you guys
next time.
All right, Shen.
It's a deal!
That's it.
It's a voice message,
not a phone call.
When I saw the message today,
saying Zeqiu was going to treat us
to a meal—
I'm not exaggerating—
I really read it 3 times.
Zeqiu would treat us to a meal?
I felt the same way.
Have I never treated you guys before?
Nope.
Exactly!
Zeqiu,
why on earth are you treating us
to this meal?
If you don't tell us, we dare not eat.
You ungrateful people
really broke my heart.
Don't talk about my brother like that.
My brother is just somewhat frugal.
We should encourage this behavior.
Then maybe he'll finally
spend more in the future.
So you are the biggest ingrate.
Alright, let's get to the point.
There is indeed some serious news
I'd like to share with everyone.
Our Dr. Lin Zhixia's
application for a national key
scientific research project
got approved.
A round of applause!
Congratulations
on achieving one more goal.
Zhixia, you really make me proud.
It's a national project!
I have something else to brag about now.
I also helped with this, right?
Shut up. Nobody asked.
Tell Mom and Dad about this later.
They will be happy for you, too.
Yeah.
Lin Zhixia has prepared
for this project for so long.
Her efforts have finally paid off.
Come on, I propose a toast
to her achievement!
-Absolutely, cheers.
-Cheers.
Hold on.
Jiang Yubai,
Zeqiu is celebrating for his sister.
So in what capacity are you
proposing this toast?
I...
As the doctor's family, of course.
Jiang, you have to drink this up.
I'll drink it up.
-Come on.
-Cheers!
Cheers.
That was a toast to Lin Zhixia.
I have one more thing to announce.
Well...
Jin Baihui and I
are getting married.
G-Getting married?
Getting married.
This is big news!
Am I the only one who didn't know?
No, I really didn't know this.
I hadn't heard a thing about it.
I only knew a tiny part of it.
I knew even less than a tiny part.
What...
Good for you, Zeqiu.
You've been working on
something so big secretly.
Baihui,
are we going to change how we address you
and call you "sister-in-law"?
Let's hear it.
Getting me to change
how I address you is not easy.
You don't need to change.
I don't mean to be a wet blanket,
but what about your parents?
We've already made up our minds.
We will be together
no matter what they say.
Hold on.
I knew
there must be
something fishy
about this rare meal you treated us to.
Lin Zhixia,
Lin Zeqiu,
you two want to use this one meal
to celebrate two happy events?
Is that appropriate?
Yeah, it shouldn't be this simple.
You should at least
treat us to another meal, right?
At least two.
Fine, fine, as many meals as you want.
Let's see if they can
stop you from whining.
Since the "sister-in-law" said so,
let's have a toast.
-Come on. Cheers.
-Cheers.
-Cheers!
Can we start eating now?
Eat up.
There's nothing else, huh?
No.
I was really happy
having dinner with everyone today.
Since you're home,
I'm heading back now.
How about you stay?
Okay.
You're going to sleep on the floor?
Yep, I'll sleep here.
Aren't you my boyfriend?
We can sleep together.
I'm so happy today.
Your heart is racing.
What's on your mind?
I'm wondering
if I can kiss you.
♪ Warm fishbowl ♪
♪ Glass sprouts forth ♪
♪ Drowning at dusk ♪
♪ You come to save me ♪
♪ Such oddities ♪
♪ Bizarre dreams ♪
♪ You call them ♪
♪ Déjà vu ♪
♪ A random cut-in ♪
♪ 2013 ♪
♪ 16 times faster ♪
♪ The night is like a window ♪
Why did you turn off the light?
To sleep.
Do you sleep with the lights on?
By sleeping, you mean...
Dad, you're here.
Mr. and Mrs. Jin.
What's this all about?
Please sit down first.
Mom, have a seat.
Well...
Mr. and Mrs. Jin,
today...
You sit down first.
I'd like to discuss with you
the relationship
between Jin Baihui and me.
We don't approve of your relationship.
You called and asked us to have a talk.
I thought you had come around.
Mom, actually, I...
Lin Zeqiu and I...
Lin,
let's make things clear today.
Our family doesn't approve
of you and Jin Baihui being together,
because I don't think
you two are a good match.
Given your family background,
your job,
and your financial situation,
you're not suitable for her in every way.
Jin Baihui should find someone
with a better background.
Of course,
you could also find someone
with a better background.
This way, you'll face much less stress
in life in the future.
We are doing this for your own good.
At your age,
you think marriage is all about love.
We got it,
because we were also once your age.
But at our age,
we know the truth about marriage.
This is the last chance
for you to change
the course of your lives.
This is a big deal,
not a joke.
Since we are on this topic,
we don't want to make things too awkward.
You two should break up peacefully.
Mr. and Mrs. Jin,
I understand what you mean.
How about we eat first?
Baihui specifically ordered
your favorite dishes.
-Let's talk over dinner.
-Actually, today...
I'm here to inform you of something.
Lin Zeqiu and I have
already registered our marriage.
What?
These are our marriage certificates.
Mr. and Mrs. Jin,
although this decision
was made a bit hastily,
we have thought it through.
Jin Baihui, are you crazy?
Mrs. Jin, this is mostly...
Shut up!
Jin Baihui,
are you going to drive me crazy?
Mr. Jin, it's all my fault.
This is on me.
Let me talk to them.
This is not because you are dissatisfied
with Lin Zeqiu,
nor is it because I didn't find
a better person to marry.
It's because I didn't listen
to your arrangements,
and I got out of your control.
That's why you are unhappy.
Dad,
Mom,
how long has it been
since we had a proper talk last time?
You only criticize me,
lecture me, and show disappointment in me.
It feels like nothing I do
is ever good enough.
But is this how we should get along?
Dad, do you remember?
When I was little, and you took me to sing
in the Children's Palace,
you told me,
"Baihui, you should sing loudly,
so I can hear your voice."
So I sang with all my strength.
No other kid could drown out my voice.
Even the teacher laughed at me.
Because that way,
you could stand outside
and hear your daughter sing.
I finally stepped onto the stage
at the school anniversary gala that year.
I know you wouldn't agree,
so I practiced
and performed in secret.
I felt so happy to be rebellious for once.
But I kept staring at the audience,
not because
the students' cheers made me proud.
I was actually trying to find you two
down there.
I was wondering.
If you saw me on stage,
if you heard my voice,
would you be
a little more satisfied with me?
Would you be happier?
Mom,
after I started school,
getting me into Qingbei University
was your everything.
You stayed up late with me,
accompanied me to exams,
and studied with me.
But how long has it been
since you went on a proper vacation?
How long has it been
since you truly lived for yourselves?
I know
how many cigarettes you smoked
on the balcony, Dad,
when I had to repeat a grade that year.
And Mom, I saw you crying secretly
in the kitchen.
I've been listening to you all these years
because...
It's not because I didn't dare to rebel.
It's because I couldn't bear to rebel.
I couldn't bear to see you hurt again.
Actually, I feel that I'm quite a failure
as a daughter.
How did I
lose the parents
who once loved me so much?
Baihui.
Dad just wanted you to live
a happier life
and go further.
Mr. and Mrs. Jin,
I understand
your concerns.
There is no parent
who doesn't love their child.
Maybe one day in the future,
when we become parents,
we might make the same choice you've made.
But today,
I hope you two
can give us a chance
and trust us this once.
I will do my best
in the rest of my life to prove
that I haven't betrayed your trust today,
and that Jin Baihui made the right choice.
Please
give me a chance.
I'm thirsty.
Pour me a cup of tea.
Mr. Jin.
Please have some tea, Mr. Jin.
Mrs. Jin, please have some tea.
I didn't prepare a gift for you.
No need, no need.
Let's eat first.
[Watch out for the train]
You're finally back, man.
I thought you weren't going to repay
this last bit of money.
No way.
Give me a moment.
[Watch out for the train]
This is the last payment.
We are even now.
You're really something.
I never expected that
you could pull through all these years.
Actually, you didn't
have to repay it back then.
But you still did it,
so your family and friends
wouldn't suffer losses.
You're a real man.
Still, thank you
for lending me the money back then.
Contact me anytime if you need anything.
After all,
we've known each other for years.
Thanks.
[Contacts]
[Peng][More]
[Delete Contact]
[Delete this contact?]
[Contacts]
Zhixia,
the project you're leading
has been included
in the national key support list.
But next,
the project is going to be upgraded,
and we will face
more complex resource integration
and management issues.
Of course,
it will also receive greater support.
So the school has decided
to make Qianche lead the later work.
You need to hand over the project
as soon as possible.
I got replaced?
But I have been in charge
of this project from the very beginning.
I'm familiar
with all the data and materials.
I've even had a plan for the next step.
How could you get me replaced
all of a sudden?
Professor,
this project was planned
and pushed forward
by Lin Zhixia alone.
I think she is fully capable
of completing the follow-up work.
Even if there's an upgrade,
we don't need to change
the person in charge, do we?
The operational difficulty
of a national project
has increased
by more than an order of magnitude.
With your current management experience,
you can't handle it.
At this stage, it would be
better for Qianche to lead.
No, I still think it's better
for Lin Zhixia
to finish this project herself.
She knows this project best.
Qianche,
there must be a reason
for the school's arrangement.
Don't you understand?
Then what will I be responsible for
after the handover?
The school and the country
have higher expectations for you.
As for your specific responsibilities,
well,
I'll tell you separately later.
[Lin Zhixia]
Why are you still up so late?
I can't sleep.
I want to chat with you.
What's wrong?
Did something happen at school?
Ms. Wu asked me
to hand the project over to Senior Tan.
I know it's not a bad thing,
but I still feel
a bit uncomfortable inside.
I think anyone would
feel uncomfortable in this situation.
After all, it's a project
you've built from scratch.
However,
it doesn't necessarily mean the professor
and the school
don't recognize your abilities.
I think
they probably want you
to focus your energy
on more important research,
right?
He said there would be
new arrangements for me.
But this project is something
we've been in charge of all along.
I was suddenly told to hand it over.
It feels like I'm detached from something
I was a part of.
I feel empty inside.
Well,
let me make an analogy
that may not be entirely accurate.
This project is like a big tree.
You helped it take root
and built its foundation layer by layer.
Therefore,
no matter how tall and big
its branches and leaves grow,
as long as it's this tree,
its roots will always be yours.
So you mean,
the roots are mine,
but the tree belongs to someone else?
Even if this tree
ends up bearing someone else's name,
Lin Zhixia,
as long as you want to,
you can even plant a whole forest
easily in the future.
Given your capabilities,
there's no need
to hold onto one single tree.
Jiang Yubai, why do you have
so much confidence in me?
It's not about confidence.
It's because I know
you're the most amazing person
I've ever met.
You have more faith in me
than I have in myself.
Alright, time to sleep.
I need to go to school
to hand it over tomorrow morning.
Good night.
Jiang Yubai, I'm missing you so much.
[Lin Zhixia]
[Jiang Yubai]
I'm coming to see you now.
[I'm coming to see you now.]
[Jiang Yubai]
It's too late. Let's meet this weekend.
I'll go meet you.
[Lin Zhixia]
Okay, I actually have something
to tell you, too.
[What is it?]
[Lin Zhixia]
What is it?
You'll know soon.
Go to sleep now. Good night.
[Something good. You'll know soon.]
[Go to sleep now. Good night.]
Good night.
[Fun Biking]
Duan, come on in.
Have a seat.
Long time no see.
[Fun Biking]
Duan,
look,
we haven't seen you at the office lately,
and everyone's lost their energy at work!
The company
really can't do without you.
Just tell me
what you want from me.
Let's cut to the chase instead of
beating around the bush.
Why isn't Mr. Duan
making a fuss this time?
I thought he'd definitely
chew us out a bit.
He's so nice this time.
Here's the thing.
Remember
the top tech expert you talked to before?
I mean Dr. Zhou,
who came back from abroad.
He is now
very popular in the market.
An investor has even made it clear
that he will immediately invest in
whichever company he chooses.
So
you want to hire Dr. Zhou now?
Duan,
I've always believed you were right.
You're really farsighted.
We all just...
Okay.
It's a deal then.
I'll find a chance to talk to him.
You're doing a good thing.
Yes.
However...
Could you not make the meeting
so tense?
What?
Are meetings this tense now without me?
We need to be more lively, right?
Yes, exactly.
Why so tense?
Yeah.
I'll have someone
buy some snacks and drinks.
Let's eat and talk. How about that?
Nice.
Good. What are we going to discuss?
Everyone, get ready. Come on.
Mr. Duan,
what a rare occasion for you
to treat me to a meal for celebration.
Do I need a reason to celebrate with you?
Come on, cheers.
You really helped me a lot
with getting this issue solved
for my company this time.
Besides, can't I just treat you to a meal?
Yes, sure.
You've grown up
and learned to be grateful.
Why are you staring at me? Eat up now.
Okay.
Nice meat...
Anything wrong?
Tell me what you're cooking up again.
Out with it
while I'm in a good mood today.
I do have something
that I want to get your take on.
Well...
A friend of mine
has a beloved one
and wants to confess his feelings to her.
But they are childhood friends.
So he doesn't know what to do.
What's so hard about it?
Just tell her directly.
Calm down. Let me finish first.
My friend is mainly afraid that
if he confesses his love to her
and gets rejected,
or if
they get together
but break up later,
they wouldn't even be friends anymore.
This girl holds
a very special place in his heart.
So,
what should he do?
Which friend of yours?
You don't know him.
Never mind which friend.
Just tell me
your take on this.
Which friend of yours don't I know?
Just tell me who it is.
Well... Forget about who it is for now.
Just answer my question first.
From a girl's perspective,
do you think this girl would agree
to be together with him?
Or rather,
if your childhood friend
confesses his love to you,
would you agree to be with him?
No.
Who would date their childhood friends?
That's ridiculous.
She is
not you.
Maybe she thinks
that growing up together
and knowing each other well
would make
for a good romantic relationship.
Right?
Y-Yeah.
Eat up.
A friend of mine
has a beloved one
and wants to confess his feelings to her.
But they are childhood friends.
If your childhood friend
confesses his love to you,
would you agree to be with him?
No.
Who would date their childhood friends?
That's ridiculous.
Maybe she thinks
that growing up together
and knowing each other well
would make
for a good romantic relationship.
You...
What are you doing?
So what if we're childhood friends?
Can't childhood friends fall in love?
I like you, Tang Tingting.
Duan Qiyan.
It's too tight. It hurts.
Let go!
If you still don't let go,
I'll stop liking you.
♪ Let me draw near to you ♪
♪ Let me imagine you ♪
♪ Let me sink into your ♪
♪ Scattered golden glow ♪
♪ Let the night blur your figure ♪
♪ Yet tear myself away from you ♪
♪ I can't fathom why ♪
♪ I've never truly possessed you ♪
♪ That blazing, radiant feeling ♪
♪ Once the rain stops, clouds disperse ♪
♪ Hence, time and again, I lose ♪
♪ Myself ♪
You never pursued me properly.
Then I'll make up
for the past 20 years first.
♪ Let the wind pass you ♪
♪ Let the dream hug you ♪
♪ Let my tears turn into your ♪
♪ Tide sinking into your eyes ♪
♪ As I told you ♪
♪ I'll never respond again ♪
♪ I thought I could ♪
♪ Forget ♪
♪ Listen to the night breeze whispering ♪
♪ It says the rain ceases
and clouds disperse ♪
♪ The rarest blessing in life
is a sweet dream ♪
Isn't this restaurant too expensive?
It's fine.
Today is very important.
What's so important?
I've paid off
all my debts.
Great, Jiang Yubai.
You are finally free.
Here's to you.
For finally getting through
the hard times,
and also for
being able to live a life
with peace and ease from now on.
Thank you
for never giving up on me.
These years,
I've had a hard time struggling.
I've cut off all contact with the world.
It felt like
my life was all about paying off debts
with no room for anything else.
But you are
like my last trace of gravity
that I can't bear to
let go of in this world.
Thank you
for not giving up on me.
Because we're binary-star companions.
We revolve around the same center.
I'm your gravity,
and you're mine.
We'll keep orbiting each other forever.
And Lin Zhixia
will love Jiang Yubai forever.
Lin Zhixia,
let's never be apart again.
Jiang Yubai.
What do you want to do
now that your debts are paid off?
What's with the sudden question?
I'm doing great now.
I make good money
with quite a stable job.
People are lining up
and even paying extra to buy my products.
But why do I always feel that
you're not really that into your work?
What makes you say so?
First of all,
you never initiate a conversation
with me about your work.
Secondly,
out of everything you do,
you're only excited about
those related to physics.
Thirdly,
you don't seem happy during most
of your working hours.
You always see
right through me like this.
So, what do you want to do next?
I want to apply to a grad program
in physics.
Great!
This is a good idea!
I support you.
Jiang Yubai can finally do
what he likes!
This is the you I know.
These lines are so great.
You die when you're forgotten by everyone.
As long as someone remembers you,
you won't really disappear.
Yeah.
My classmates have seen
movies in dome theaters,
in 3D,
and on IMAX screens.
But they definitely haven't watched one
projected in a hospital ward.
I scored a point.
When you recover,
you can continue your studies,
fall in love,
get married,
and see the world.
You can score many more points.
Then I definitely won't study medicine.
I've really had enough of hospitals.
Then what do you want to do?
I want to be a ship captain.
It's so free
to sail through wind and waves.
No way.
I'd better stay on land.
I like crowded places,
with hustle and bustle.
I'll open a drink stall at a night market.
When the clock strikes 12,
I'll treat everyone to milk tea.
When everyone is happy,
they'll all surround me,
singing and dancing,
wishing for prosperity.
It'll be so much fun.
I want to
sell swim rings by the pool,
with the colorful ones
filling the whole pool.
I want to
open a cat cafe by the school gate.
I also want to...
Sounds great.
Dr. Shen,
what does it feel like
to be in love with someone?
I haven't had the chance
to love someone properly.
Being in love with someone
makes you very happy.
Sometimes...
it also makes you sad.
It sounds like the feeling of being alive.
The movie says
a person dies 3 times.
The first time is
when the heart stops beating.
The second time is
when you're forgotten,
and people no longer talk about you.
The third time is
when the last person in the world
who remembered you
forgets you, too.
Dr. Shen,
I'm a bit scared all of a sudden.
If one day
no one in the world remembers me,
would it really be as if I never existed?
I will always remember you.
Dr. Shen,
I will remember you, too.
Even if I am forgotten
by the last person who remembered me,
before falling
into the boundless darkness,
I will still remember you for sure.
Pinky swear.
Dao, go load the luggage first.
I'll have a word with Dr. Shen.
Okay.
Take this
as a keepsake.
Next time you are bored,
you can take it out and look at it.
[Hematology Department Shen Fuxuan]
Stick it on yourself.
[Hematology Department, Shen Fuxuan]
[Huacheng City Hejia Hospital]
Dr. Shen.
Treat me to a movie
when I get back, would you?
I'll pay for every movie you want to watch
after you get back.
That's going to cost you a lot.
I'm leaving.
Shui, I...
Goodbye,
Dr. Shen.
Liu,
I'm going to apply to a grad program.
You've finally come around.
I told you long ago
that it would be a waste
of your talent to be
just a craftsman.
Since you want to apply to a grad program,
try to be my student.
How's it?
I'm not interested.
How arrogant.
So what are you interested in?
Particle physics.
Are you crazy, boy?
This major is
unpopular and hard to get into.
It's also not easy
to achieve results in the future.
I don't care.
You should just follow me.
I can teach you this, too.
Liu,
I know what you're thinking.
If I become your student,
I'll have to fish with you every day.
I'll also have to work for you
when I'm free,
like fixing speakers
and modifying fishing rods.
Fish with me every day?
You think I like seeing your sour face?
I'm just afraid
you will fail in your application, okay?
Do you think it's that easy
to apply to a grad program?
Besides,
so many people are
dying to be my students.
Don't be ungrateful.
Don't worry.
If I fail,
I'll fish with you every day.
[Confidential Files]
Zhixia,
I need to talk to you
about something
extremely important.
I know
your project
has been going very smoothly lately,
and your team is very cohesive.
But the school just received a notice.
Our country has
a high-level classified research project
that we're
looking for suitable talent to join.
Your name is at the top of the list.
A classified project?
What do you want me to do?
The work isn't much different from
your research at school.
With your abilities,
you should be able to adapt quickly.
The only difference is that,
from the moment you are transferred,
you must devote yourself
entirely to the work
in a closed-off environment.
Due to the significance of the project,
strict confidentiality is required.
You cannot reveal anything
even to your closest friends.
This is a matter of principle.
This is a very rare opportunity.
Working on a major national project
may not bring you recognition
right away,
but its results
will push a certain field
forward by a giant leap.
As a researcher,
you might get this kind
of opportunity only once in a lifetime.
Leave it there.
I'll wash it later.
W-What did you just say?
Did something happen when you got back
from school today?
I can't tell you.
You can't even tell me?
Professor Wu told me
not to tell anyone about it.
Fine.
If you're not telling me,
let me guess.
Is it about work?
Is it about the project
you were transferred from?
Your previous project
was already a key national project.
The fact that they transferred you
away from it
means there's a more important project
that needs you.
So you can't talk about it.
I'll ask no more.
If I go,
we might not see each other
for a long time.
Actually, I feel
the same way you do.
If this is what you want to do,
you have my support.
I hope you can become the person
you want to be.
For all these years,
you've been my only source of comfort.
Now,
it's time for me to be your support.
♪ Only for this lingering warmth
of the moment ♪
♪ Trading souls with the night ♪
♪ Every dusk I have stolen ♪
♪ Foretells a parting ♪
♪ Where did the storm start brewing ♪
♪ Drenching you before we knew it? ♪
♪ Let me draw near to you ♪
♪ Let me imagine you ♪
♪ Let me sink into your ♪
♪ Scattered golden glow ♪
♪ Let the night blur your figure ♪
♪ Yet tear myself away from you ♪
♪ I can't fathom why ♪
♪ I've never truly possessed you ♪
♪ That blazing, radiant feeling ♪
♪ Once the rain stops, clouds disperse ♪
♪ Hence, time and again, I lose ♪
Professor Wu Qingxi said that
["The Universe, the Stars, and You"]
this kind of confidential project
could be
♪ Myself ♪
a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity
for a researcher.
But I must leave the city,
leave my family,
and leave Jiang Yubai.
Yet Jiang Yubai told me without hesitation
that he would be my support
and let me fly high.
He is like my Einstein field equation.
Just like the curvature of spacetime
and the motion of matter,
we are bound together.